It's starting to get colder.
I like it better than the heat. It feels so crisp outside.
Yeah, yeah, that's great. Now, could you tell me where we're going, Shinoa?
Huh? Relying on you to navigate for us is getting kind of annoying.
Well, if we stay on this road, we'll eventually end up in Hakone.
There, we could soak in the hot spring, eat a feast, and then wake up relaxed and refreshed.
Doesn't that sound like paradise, you guys?
Sure.
We're really headed to Ebina.
Ebina, huh? I don't think I've heard of it.
Honestly, I'd rather go to Hakone.
Oh, definitely. But I'm afraid a vacation just isn't in the cards.
Nagoya is our final destination.
Nagoya? Are you there, Mika?
Crap, they came out of nowhere!
Kill them!
Go! Picture you!
Not slowing down.
No problem. Come on, Hashiromaru!
Kimizuki, another one. Hard right, quick!
What?
Come on, can't we go faster?
Bye-bye, we'll see you in Ebina!
Hey! Wait, where the hell are you going?
Seriously?
What do you think?
Why are you creeping around, Ghoshi?
Hey, look, Curran. You like?
Do I like what?
a little light reading it's been a long time since we've seen girls lounging around in fancy
underwear i can't even get shigure or sayuri to wear bathing suits ask me to again and i'll
gouge your eyes out i guess i'd have to wear one if the lieutenant colonel ordered me to that is
did you hear that current for the sake of morale tell her to fight the bathing suit
will you shut up you're supposed to be checking for vampires oh yeah mito's keeping an eye out how can
you be so useless current i finished scoping out the interior there are no signs that vampires have
been here hey mito question would you wear a swimsuit why are you asking me that well pervert
gurin over here wants to know what your body looks like under that uniform what but i what kind of
dirty things have you been talking about do you really want to know current look the troops have
started to arrive don't ignore me
Good morning.
Whoa, Xinya, where'd you get a car like this?
It was abandoned on the side of the road, so I hotwired it.
Awesome, huh?
It's perfect for an impractical major general like you.
What are you doing here?
Brother Curito told me about your mission.
Sounds like you guys are sacrificial pawns.
A hundred troops don't stand much of a chance against the vampire nobles.
Those bloodsuckers are too powerful.
So I figured, why not bring my impractical self here and see if I can help out?
Okay, you can thank me now.
You're such a moron.
Well, now we're definitely gonna be late.
Um, do you think we'll get in trouble?
If Garin's mad, I'll just tell him it was Shinawa and Mitsuba's fault.
How dare you sell out your comrades?
Comrades, my ass. You tried to leave me behind.
Hey, we went back and picked you up eventually.
We'll leave here at 0700 hours.
Six hours later, we will arrive in Nagoya.
The directives I hand out will cover specific strategic details.
Oh, nice of you to show up!
I'm surprised you didn't miss the entire war.
Well, you see, sir, we have a really good excuse for being late.
It's not like we stopped at the hot springs for a long luxurious bath.
Don't make excuses!
This mission isn't some childish game.
If you can't follow orders, leave now!
Damn kid, screwing around.
Sorry, Lieutenant Colonel.
This is my fault. I take all the blame.
You?
We were late because I took it upon myself to fight the four horsemen of John.
Does that mean you're going to leave?
No, sir. Please let me stay.
I want to help destroy the vampires.
Fall in line with the others.
Just know, you'll have to face severe punishment later.
You know...
Listen to me carefully, everyone.
During this mission, I won't tolerate any failures.
Follow my orders to the letter and don't fool around.
This mission will probably be the most dangerous you will ever have.
Many of you will die.
Remember, everyone here is family.
That means those who fall in battle are our brothers and sisters.
But they won't die in vain.
Their sacrifices will ensure our success.
Let me be clear.
Our goal isn't to come back alive.
It is to be victorious no matter what.
Do you understand me?
Yeah!
I just want to apologize.
This was all my fault.
Hey, don't sweat it.
What's the worst that Gurren can do to me?
You can take all the blame next time.
Special private Yuichiro Hyakuya!
We're waiting.
Okay.
It's time for me to get an earful.
No, wait.
Let me go in with you and explain.
Yeah.
And I was screwing around on the road, too.
I'll tell Gurren.
Well, if this is a party, I guess I might as well come for backup.
Yeah, me too.
Nah, don't worry about it, guys.
I'm kind of used to Gurren yelling at me anyway.
But you...
Lieutenant Colonel Gurren.
He's here.
Hey, idiot you.
How's it going?
Huh?
Why would you ask me a question like that when you're getting ready to lecture me?
But none of this was your fault, was it?
Uh, well...
Taking the heat for your comrades is admirable.
So what?
You brought me here to reward me?
Oh, now you understand.
Our Gurren here is actually a big softie.
Huh?
Hey, wait!
You're that guy from that place I had to go that time.
You certainly don't have a gift for words, but you're right.
Good to see you.
That's enough.
We're wasting time here.
Goshi, let's get started.
Yeah, yeah.
Ew!
Hot, hot, very hot!
I'm burning alive, you bastard!
Come on, get me down from here!
What?
Whoa!
No, no, no, no, no!
Hey!
An illusion spell?
What kind of sick joke are you trying to pull, Gurren?
It's no joke.
This is your punishment, Shinoa.
This is what you get for not fessing up yourself.
I'm here to show you that not following orders can easily get your comrades killed.
Yes, I know that.
And I'm well aware that what I did was wrong.
That's not good enough.
You've never experienced what it's like to truly care for another person.
And therefore, you don't understand the fear of losing someone.
But from now on, things are different.
One wrong move could get your comrades killed.
As team leader, their lives are in your hands.
I said I know that.
And I said that's not enough, brat.
Remember?
Let me ask you something.
What would you do if a huge threat suddenly appeared right now?
Would you be able to manage your team?
Right, let's see.
A little test pitting me, Mito, and Shinya against you and your squad.
The fight begins in ten seconds.
Ten.
Nine.
What?
Eight.
You seriously want us to fight?
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Come on, we need to put some distance between us and them.
Three.
Hmm.
You shouldn't be so tough on Shinoa.
You know she's trying really hard.
That's awfully sweet of you.
Why don't you show her your support by beating us instead of standing here looking stupid?
Okay, but don't blame me when I embarrass you.
Like I'd lose to some kid.
First, I want to put the long-range fighters up against each other.
That's Yoichi versus Major General Shinya.
Got it.
Based on what I know about Colonel Jujo, Mitsu and I should be able to hold her off.
So our only real problem is Gurin?
Yes.
The lieutenant colonel is a master of close quarters combat.
Kimizuki and you will team up.
If he manages to beat you two, then this test is as good as over.
No sweat, we just have to take him down.
Yeah, I've been waiting to get a piece of that loser.
All right, take your positions.
Okay, kids.
Here we come.
Shinya, allow me.
Come on, Byakomaru.
Get them.
They're formation is already falling apart.
Everyone, regroup.
I'll cover our backs.
You're not getting away, rookie.
Let's do this.
I won't let you pass me, Gurin!
You're an idiot.
Hey, you're not half bad.
Of course!
The fight is over, children.
Come on, Gurin.
Was that really necessary?
Try not to cry.
I'm not done with you!
That's it!
Everyone get into formation with you in the center!
Whoa, Lieutenant Colonel Gurin is fighting those newbies.
This must be some kind of punishment for being late.
Wow, look at that kid.
Yeah, he's matching with the Lieutenant Colonel's attacks pretty well.
There's no way the kid will beat him with power alone.
What the hell?
It's an explosion spell.
Let me disenchant it.
Not a chance.
Now's the time to admit defeat before I blow your head off.
If I explode, then I'm taking you with me!
Whoa, no, I'm terrified.
I'm just kidding.
I figured you'd try something.
There, I'm past your defenses.
That means all your comrades are dead now.
Damn it!
You!
I'll stop you!
You should never challenge someone who is stronger than you are.
And you guys are way too late.
Stupid!
What a disappointment.
You've got three Black Demon holders in your squad, and this is the best you can do?
The nobles are stronger than we are, and they won't hold back.
Do you really think you stand a chance against them?
All right.
As you can see, these rookies need a lot of help.
We're gonna have to show them what it means to be good comrades.
Are we totally sure those three guys have Black Demon weapons?
How'd they manage the trials?
The weapons don't matter.
Without teamwork, they're all useless.
Guess that's why we gotta look after them.
What's wrong? You look dissatisfied.
I am.
I'm thinking about what strategy we should use the next time we face off against your team.
Oh, so the hot-headed little rebel has brains as well.
Why are you touching me?
This test pointed out your weaknesses.
Focus on your teamwork.
Excuse me. May I speak freely, sir?
These kids are dangerous.
Newbies have no place on the battlefield.
They don't follow orders or obey rules, and they have no sense of teamwork.
If you let them join us, they'll only drag us down.
Hmm. Those are all problems, but how do we fix them?
Oh, wait. I know.
I'm putting your team in charge of them.
Shikure, rearrange the team rosters.
I want Shinoa's squad to join up with Narubis.
Yes, sir.
Wait. Please rethink this, Lieutenant Colonel.
This is Sergeant Makoto Narubi.
And that's Rika Inoue, Taro Kageyama, Yayoi Endo, and Chusaku Iwasaki.
They're an excellent squad.
They'll train you well.
They don't seem too thrilled to have us.
Please, sir.
Listen up. Playtime's over, so let's focus. We've got a mission.
Sir!
I'm looking forward to serving with you.
Thanks. You had to go and open your big mouth, didn't you?
Do you realize how much work this is?
Well, they do seem to have a lot of raw power.
With a little training, maybe they'll turn out to be useful.
What's with that sergeant?
You can't really blame him.
He may be a complete jerk-off, but he's dead right about us.
Hey, everyone.
I'm sorry about how things turned out.
All of this stuff is my fault.
Not just being late.
We lost because I'm incompetent.
I don't think I'm fit to be called the commander.
Don't say that.
Did you not hear what Gurren said?
All we need to do is learn to work as a team.
And the first step is supporting each other.
We're a family.
The more we work together, the stronger we'll be.
Yeah.
And that means we still need a commander.
So what do you think, Shinawa?
Okay.
Vampires!
Vampires are coming!
No! Please don't hurt me!
They're gifts for the nobles in Nagoya.
If you want to take a little sip, now's the time, Mika.
I'm not interested in drinking human blood.
Wait, is that some kind of joke?
If you're afraid of getting caught, don't worry.
You can trust me. I won't tell a soul.
What a weirdo.
The day will come when you will have to drink from a human.
No! Stop! Please! I'm not going with you!
See there? I knew you looked thirsty.
Yes, definitely a weirdo.
There is no warning.
Teach him to make meteor.
The Goat.
The Goat is still up.
We'll be right back.
Next time on Seraph of the End, Livestock Revolt.